This time they messed with the wrong guy!
Bullet is a action, crime, thriller film directed by Nick Lyon.
Danny Trejo plays 'Bullet' a tough cop who takes the law into
his own hands when his grandson is kidnapped.
Frank, played by Danny Trejo.
Jessica, played by Seri DeYoung.
Kruger, played by Torsten Voges.
Carlito Kane, played by Jonathan Banks.
Mario, played by Kyle Villalovos.
Samantha, played by Eve Mauro.
Bullet (stylized as BULLET) is a 2014 action thriller film starring Danny
Trejo as the title character and Jonathan Banks as the villain.
The film was directed and co-written by Nick Lyon, with additional writing by Matthew Joynes, Ron
Peer and Byron Lester, and was produced by Matthew Joynes and Robert Rodriguez.
It follows an undercover police officer-turned-vigilante (Trejo)
tracking down the crooks who kidnapped his grandson.
Filming took place in Los Angeles, United States.
The film was released on Blu-ray and DVD on February 25, 2014 in North America.
The film explores themes of corruption, kidnapping, drugs.
The tone is intense.